A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1952-1957 FA425
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1956
  - United States, 1956; 1956/200
    - United States - (Uj-United H), 1956 (Box 36, Folder 238)
    - United States - United States - Agriculture - (A-H), 1956 (Box 37, Folder 239)
    - United States - United States - Agriculture - Industrial Use of Agricultural Products, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 240)
    - United States - United States - Agriculture - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 37, Folder 241)
    - United States - United States - (Ai-Information), 1956 (Box 37, Folder 242)
    - United States - United States - (Ai-Information), 1956 (Box 37, Folder 243)
    - United States - United States - (Ai-Information), 1956 (Box 37, Folder 244)
    - United States - United States - (Ai-Information), 1956 (Box 37, Folder 245)
    - United States - United States - (Interior-ICA/F), 1956 (Box 38, Folder 246)
    - United States - United States - (ICA/H-Steel), 1956 (Box 38, Folder 247)
    - United States - United States - (ICA/H-Steel), 1956 (Box 38, Folder 248)
    - United States - United States - (ICA/H-Steel), 1956 (Box 38, Folder 249)
    - United States - United States - (ICA/H-Steel), 1956 (Box 38, Folder 250)
    - United States - United States - (ICA/H-Steel), 1956 (Box 38, Folder 251)
    - United States - University - (A-Chicago/F), 1956 (Box 39, Folder 252)
    - United States - University - (A-Chicago/F), 1956 (Box 39, Folder 253)
    - United States - University - (A-Chicago/F), 1956 (Box 39, Folder 254)
    - United States - University - (A-Chicago/F), 1956 (Box 39, Folder 255)
    - United States - University - (A-Chicago/F), 1956 (Box 39, Folder 256)
    - United States - University - (A-Chicago/F), 1956 (Box 39, Folder 257)
    - United States - University - (A-Chicago/F), 1956 (Box 39, Folder 258)
    - United States - University - (Chicago/H-Michigan/J), 1956 (Box 40, Folder 259)
    - United States - University - (Chicago/H-Michigan/J), 1956 (Box 40, Folder 260)
    - United States - University - (Chicago/H-Michigan/J), 1956 (Box 40, Folder 261)
    - United States - University - (Chicago/H-Michigan/J), 1956 (Box 40, Folder 262)
    - United States - University - (Chicago/H-Michigan/J), 1956 (Box 40, Folder 263)
    - United States - University - (Chicago/H-Michigan/J), 1956 (Box 40, Folder 264)
    - United States - University - (Michigan/Z-RH), 1956 (Box 41, Folder 265)
    - United States - University - (Michigan/Z-RH), 1956 (Box 41, Folder 266)
    - United States - University - (Michigan/Z-RH), 1956 (Box 41, Folder 267)
    - United States - University - (Michigan/Z-RH), 1956 (Box 41, Folder 268)
    - United States - University - (Michigan/Z-RH), 1956 (Box 41, Folder 269)
    - United States - University - (Michigan/Z-RH), 1956 (Box 41, Folder 270)
    - United States - University - (Ro-W), 1956 (Box 42, Folder 271)
    - United States - University - (Ro-W), 1956 (Box 42, Folder 272)
    - United States - University - (Ro-W), 1956 (Box 42, Folder 273)
    - United States - University - (Ro-W), 1956 (Box 42, Folder 274)
    - United States - (U-V), 1956 (Box 42, Folder 275)
    - United States - (Wa-Weh), 1956 (Box 42, Folder 276)
    - United States - (Wei-Wy), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 277)
    - United States - (Wei-Wy), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 278)
    - United States - (Wei-Wy), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 279)
    - United States - (Wei-Wy), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 280)
    - United States - (X-Yah), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 281)
    - United States - Yale University - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 282)
    - United States - Yale University - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 283)
    - United States - (Ye-Z), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 284)
    - United States - ANTA - Far Eastern Association, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 515)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/200.A
      - United States - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 285)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 286)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 287)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 288)
      - United States - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 289)
    - United States - Nursing, 1956; 1956/200.C
      - United States - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 290)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/200.R
      - United States - American Council of Learned Societies, Jan-May 11, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 291)
      - United States - American Council of Learned Societies, May 16-Dec, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 292)
      - United States - (C-Z), 1956 (Box 45, Folder 294)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/200.S
      - United States - (A-S), 1956 (Box 45, Folder 295)
      - United States - (A-S), 1956 (Box 45, Folder 296)
      - United States - (A-S), 1956 (Box 45, Folder 297)
      - United States - (A-S), 1956 (Box 45, Folder 298)
      - United States - (S-W), 1956 (Box 46, Folder 299)
      - United States - (S-W), 1956 (Box 46, Folder 300)
      - United States - (S-W), 1956 (Box 46, Folder 301)
  - Alaska, 1956; 1956/202
    - Alaska, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 302)
    - Alaska - Declinations, 1956; 1956/202.F
      - Alaska, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 302)
      - United States - American Council of Learned Societies - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 45, Folder 293)
  - California, 1956; 1956/205
    - California, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 302)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1956; 1956/206
    - Canal Zone, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 302)
    - Canal Zone, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 302)
    - Panama Canal Zone - Declinations, 1956; 1956/206.F
      - Canal Zone, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 302)
  - Guam, 1956; 1956/213
    - Guam, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 302)
  - Hawaii, 1956; 1956/214
    - Hawaii, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 303)
    - Hawaii - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/214.D
      - Hawaii, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 303)
  - New Mexico, 1956; 1956/235
    - New Mexico, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 304)
  - Philippines, 1956; 1956/242
    - Philippine Republic, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 304)
    - Philippines - (A-P), 1956 (Box 46, Folder 305)
    - Philippines - (A-P), 1956 (Box 46, Folder 306)
    - Philippines - (Q-Z), 1956 (Box 47, Folder 307)
    - Philippines - (Q-Z), 1956 (Box 47, Folder 308)
    - Philippines - (Q-Z), 1956 (Box 47, Folder 309)
    - Philippine Republic - Benitez, C., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 517)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/242.E
      - Philippines - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 47, Folder 310)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/242.R
      - Philippines - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 47, Folder 310)
  - Puerto Rico, 1956; 1956/243
    - Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 311)
    - Puerto Rico - (A-Po), 1956 (Box 47, Folder 312)
    - Puerto Rico - (Pu-R), 1956 (Box 47, Folder 0312A)
    - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 313)
    - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 314)
    - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 315)
    - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 316)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/243.A
      - Puerto Rico - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 48, Folder 317)
    - Puerto Rico - Nursing, 1956; 1956/243.C
      - Puerto Rico - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 48, Folder 318)
    - Puerto Rico - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/243.S
      - Puerto Rico - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 48, Folder 318)
  - South America, 1956; 1956/300
    - South America and Latin America - Administration, Jan-Mar 1956 (Box 48, Folder 319)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration, Apr-Dec 1956 (Box 49, Folder 320)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration, Apr-Dec 1956 (Box 49, Folder 321)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 49, Folder 322)
    - South America and Latin America - (I-Z), 1956 (Box 49, Folder 323)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/300.A
      - South America and Latin America - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 49, Folder 324)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/300.E
      - South America and Latin America - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 49, Folder 324)
    - South America and Latin America - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/300.R
      - South America and Latin America - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 49, Folder 324)
  - Argentina, 1956; 1956/301
    - Argentina - (A-S), 1956 (Box 49, Folder 325)
    - Argentina - (U-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 326)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/301.A
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 327)
    - Argentina - Nursing, 1956; 1956/301.C
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 327)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/301.D
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 327)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/301.E
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 327)
    - Argentina - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/301.R
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 327)
  - Bolivia, 1956; 1956/303
    - Bolivia, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 328)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/303.E
      - Bolivia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 328)
  - Brazil, 1956; 1956/305
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 329)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 330)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 331)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 332)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 50, Folder 333)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 518)
    - Brazil - (E-Z), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 519)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/305.A
      - Brazil - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 51, Folder 334)
    - Brazil - Nursing, 1956; 1956/305.C
      - Brazil, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 335)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/305.D
      - Brazil, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 335)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/305.E
      - Brazil - (A-Ca), 1956 (Box 51, Folder 335)
      - Brazil - (Co-Z), 1956 (Box 51, Folder 336)
    - Brazil - Malaria, 1956; 1956/305.I
      - Brazil, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 336)
    - Brazil - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/305.S
      - Brazil, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 336)
  - Chile, 1956; 1956/309
    - Chile - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 51, Folder 337)
    - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/309.A
      - Chile, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 338)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1956; 1956/309.C
      - Chile, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 338)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/309.D
      - Chile - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 51, Folder 338)
      - Chile - Munoz Pizarro, C., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 519)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/309.E
      - Chile, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 339)
    - Chile - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/309.S
      - Chile, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 339)
  - Colombia, 1956; 1956/311
    - Colombia, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 340)
    - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 52, Folder 341)
    - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 52, Folder 342)
    - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 52, Folder 343)
    - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 52, Folder 344)
    - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 520)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/311.A
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 52, Folder 345)
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 521)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/311.D
      - Colombia - Agriculture, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 0345A)
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 52, Folder 346)
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 521)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/311.E
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 52, Folder 346)
    - Colombia - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/311.R
      - Colombia, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 347)
    - Colombia - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/311.S
      - Colombia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 347)
  - Costa Rica, 1956; 1956/313
    - Costa Rica, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 348)
    - Costa Rica - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/313.A
      - Costa Rica - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 348)
    - Costa Rica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/313.D
      - Costa Rica - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 348)
    - Costa Rica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/313.E
      - Costa Rica - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 348)
  - Cuba, 1956; 1956/315
    - Cuba, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 349)
    - Cuba - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/315.D
      - Cuba - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 349)
  - Ecuador, 1956; 1956/317
    - Ecuador, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 350)
    - Ecuador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/317.D
      - Ecuador - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 350)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/317.E
      - Ecuador - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 350)
  - Guatemala, 1956; 1956/319
    - Guatemala, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 351)
  - Haiti, 1956; 1956/320
    - Haiti, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 351)
    - Haiti - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/320.E
      - Haiti - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 351)
  - Honduras, 1956; 1956/321
    - Honduras - Escuela Agricola Pan Americana, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 352)
    - Honduras - Escuela Agricola Pan Americana, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 0352A)
    - Honduras, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 353)
    - Honduras - Declinations, 1956; 1956/321.F
      - Honduras - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 353)
  - Mexico, 1956; 1956/323
    - Mexico - (A-T), 1956 (Box 54, Folder 354)
    - Mexico - (A-T), 1956 (Box 54, Folder 355)
    - Mexico - (A-T), 1956 (Box 54, Folder 356)
    - Mexico - (A-T), 1956 (Box 54, Folder 357)
    - Mexico - (A-T), 1956 (Box 54, Folder 358)
    - Mexico - (U-Z), 1956 (Box 55, Folder 359)
    - Mexico - (U-Z), 1956 (Box 55, Folder 360)
    - Mexico - (U-Z), 1956 (Box 55, Folder 361)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/323.A
      - Mexico - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 55, Folder 362)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/323.E
      - Mexico - (A-G), 1956 (Box 55, Folder 363)
      - Mexico - (L-Z), 1956 (Box 55, Folder 364)
    - Mexico - Malaria, 1956; 1956/323.I
      - Mexico - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 365)
    - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/323.R
      - Mexico - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 365)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/323.S
      - Mexico - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 365)
  - Nicaragua, 1956; 1956/325
    - Nicaragua, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 366)
    - Nicaragua - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/325.D
      - Nicaragua, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 366)
  - Panama, 1956; 1956/327
    - Panama, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 366)
    - Panama - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/327.A
      - Panama, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 366)
    - Panama - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/327.D
      - Panama, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 366)
  - Paraguay, 1956; 1956/329
    - Paraguay, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 367)
    - Paraguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/329.D
      - Paraguay - A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 367)
  - Peru, 1956; 1956/331
    - Peru, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 368)
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/331.A
      - Peru - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 368)
    - Peru - Nursing, 1956; 1956/331.C
      - Peru - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 369)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/331.D
      - Peru - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 369)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/331.E
      - Peru - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 369)
  - El Salvador, 1956; 1956/333
    - El Salvador, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 370)
    - El Salvador - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/333.A
      - El Salvador, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 370)
    - El Salvador - Malaria, 1956; 1956/333.I
      - El Salvador, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 370)
  - Uruguay, 1956; 1956/337
    - Uruguay, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 370)
    - Uruguay - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/337.A
      - Uruguay, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 370)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/337.D
      - Uruguay, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 370)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/337.E
      - Uruguay, 1956 (Box 56, Folder 370)
  - Venezuela, 1956; 1956/339
    - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 371)
    - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 372)
    - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 522)
    - Venezuela - Nursing, 1956; 1956/339.C
      - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 373)
    - Venezuela - Malaria, 1956; 1956/339.I
      - Venezuela - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 373)
  - Great Britain, 1956; 1956/400
    - Great Britain - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 374)
  - England, 1956; 1956/401
    - England - (A-I), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 375)
    - England - (A-I), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 376)
    - England - (A-I), 1956 (Box 57, Folder 377)
    - England - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 58, Folder 378)
    - England - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 58, Folder 379)
    - England - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 58, Folder 380)
    - England - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 58, Folder 381)
    - England - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 58, Folder 382)
    - England - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 58, Folder 383)
    - England - (J-Z), 1956 (Box 58, Folder 384)
    - England - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 522)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/401.A
      - England - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 385)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/401.D
      - England - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 385)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/401.E
      - England - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 385)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/401.R
      - England - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 386)
      - England - University of Manchester - American Studies, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 523)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/401.S
      - England - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 386)
  - Ireland, 1956; 1956/403
    - Ireland, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 387)
    - Ireland - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/403.R
      - Ireland, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 387)
  - Scotland, 1956; 1956/405
    - Scotland, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 387)
    - Scotland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/405.E
      - Scotland, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 387)
  - Wales, 1956; 1956/407
    - Wales - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 388)
  - Australia, 1956; 1956/410
    - Australia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 389)
    - Australia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 390)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/410.A
      - Australia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 391)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/410.E
      - Australia - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 59, Folder 391)
  - New Zealand, 1956; 1956/418
    - New Zealand, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 392)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/418.A
      - New Zealand, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 392)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 392)
  - Caribbean Region, 1956; 1956/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 392)
  - Guyana, 1956; 1956/423
    - Guyana, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 392)
  - Belize, 1956; 1956/425
    - Belize - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/425.D
      - Belize, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 392)
  - Canada, 1956; 1956/427
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 393)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 394)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 395)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 396)
    - Canada - Pugwash Conference, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 524)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/427.A
      - Canada - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/427.E
      - Canada - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/427.R
      - Canada - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
  - Jamaica, 1956; 1956/437
    - Jamaica, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/437.A
      - Jamaica, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
    - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/437.E
      - Jamaica, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
  - Trinidad, 1956; 1956/451
    - Trinidad and Tobago, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
    - Trinidad and Tobago - Imperial College of Tropical Agriculture, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 524)
    - Trinidad - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/451.E
      - Trinidad and Tobago, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
    - Trinidad - Malaria, 1956; 1956/451.I
      - Trinidad and Tobago, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
      - Trinidad and Tobago, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 524)
  - Windward Islands, 1956; 1956/455
    - Windward Islands, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 397)
  - South Asia, 1956; 1956/460
    - South Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/460.R
      - South Asia - "Diary of a Trip to South Asia by Chadbourne Gilpatric", Jan 8-Feb 13 1956; Incomplete (Box 60, Folder 0397A)
  - Sri Lanka (Ceylon), 1956; 1956/462
    - Sri Lanka, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 398)
    - Sri Lanka (Ceylon) - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/462.A
      - Sri Lanka, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 398)
    - Sri Lanka (Ceylon) - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/462.D
      - Sri Lanka, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 398)
    - Sri Lanka (Ceylon) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/462.E
      - Sri Lanka, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 398)
    - Sri Lanka (Ceylon) - Malaria, 1956; 1956/462.I
      - Sri Lanka, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 398)
  - Hong Kong, 1956; 1956/463
    - Hong Kong, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 398)
    - Hong Kong - University of Hong Kong, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 525)
  - India, 1956; 1956/464
    - India - (A-Ah), 1956 (Box 60, Folder 399)
    - India - (Ak-Az), 1956 (Box 61, Folder 400)
    - India - (B-K), 1956 (Box 61, Folder 401)
    - India - (B-K), 1956 (Box 61, Folder 402)
    - India - (B-K), 1956 (Box 61, Folder 403)
    - India - (B-K), 1956 (Box 61, Folder 404)
    - India - (B-K), 1956 (Box 61, Folder 405)
    - India - (L-University of Bombay/E), 1956 (Box 62, Folder 406)
    - India - (L-University of Bombay/E), 1956 (Box 62, Folder 407)
    - India - (L-University of Bombay/E), 1956 (Box 62, Folder 408)
    - India - (L-University of Bombay/E), 1956 (Box 62, Folder 409)
    - India - (L-University of Bombay/E), 1956 (Box 62, Folder 410)
    - India - (University of Bombay/S - University/D), 1956 (Box 62, Folder 411)
    - India - (University Grants - Z), 1956 (Box 62, Folder 412)
    - India - Indian Statistical Institute, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 525)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/464.A
      - India - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 413)
    - India - Nursing, 1956; 1956/464.C
      - India - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 413)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/464.D
      - India - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 414)
      - India, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 525)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/464.E
      - India - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 415)
      - India - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 416)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1956; 1956/464.R
      - India - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 417)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1956; 1956/464.S
      - India - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 417)
  - Pakistan, 1956; 1956/465
    - Pakistan - (A-D), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 418)
    - Pakistan - (E-P), 1956 (Box 63, Folder 419)
    - Pakistan - (S-Z), 1956 (Box 64, Folder 420)
    - Pakistan - Mayo School of Art, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 526)
    - Pakistan - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/465.A
      - Pakistan - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 64, Folder 421)
    - Pakistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1956; 1956/465.D
      - Pakistan - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 64, Folder 421)
    - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1956; 1956/465.E
      - Pakistan - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 64, Folder 421)
      - Pakistan, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 526)
  - Burma, 1956; 1956/468
    - Burma, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 422)
    - Burma - Medical Sciences, 1956; 1956/468.A
      - Burma - (A-Z), 1956 (Box 64, Folder 422)